Hi, my name is Anna and I am designer with almost 5 years of experience.

I design digital products, interfaces, and mobile apps for clients in IoT, medicine, and tech. I'm passionate about creating tools and experiences that improve user life.

Visit my website to find more, or email me if you have a question, or want to chat:

<u>annayushch.com</u> <u>annayushch@gmail.com</u>

Experience

2020.11 - 2021.04

MD Digital

Did a complete redesign for telehealth service, built new functionality within the company's pivot. Contributed to the creation of a new design system from scratch

2020.11 - 2021.04

Datasys + Searched

Took part in the interface design and website design for a full-service provider of data, analytics, and digital media solutions

2020.04 - 2020.10

NDA client

Drove the end-to-end design process and decisions from defining the customer journey for the 4 user roles to final mockups and validation through user testing for active producer of charging solutions for electric vehicles

2020.01 - 2020.03

SparkySpot

Created a marketplace website where job seekers can handle their CV, and designed creative resume builder

2019.07 - 2019.12

Ars Data

Contributed to the development of interfaces to visualize data that comes from the oil production platform in real-time and helps the station operator make complex decisions in crisis situations. Created a website, and visual design/branding

2017.07 - 2019.07

Lazarev agency

Developed websites, interfaces, admin panels, mobile apps, and other UX/UI design projects

2016.12 - 2017.07

The 23.design

Developed landing pages and interfaces for Ukrainian (Ivan Dorn, Biopharma, Metinvest) and worldwide clients

Education

2021.04 - 2021.05

Projector

Mobile Interfaces Advanced

2020

HTML Academy

HTML and CSS basics

2020

Bangbang Education

UX design

2016.09 - 2017.01

Projector

Web design

2010 - 2015

Kyiv National

Economics University

Master's Degree, Human Resource Management, sociology and psychology faculty

Skills

- User experience design
- User interface design
- iOS and Andriod apps
- Responsive design
- Sketching and wireframing
- Prototyping
- Data visualization
- Researching
- Product thinking
- Writing skills
- Using frameworks

Interests

- Fiction and Non-fiction
- Kickboxing and Thai boxing
- PS videogames
- Hiking trips
- Psychology and meditation
- Collecting vinyl
- Collecting internet pieces